(Howard:)- Next time, make your own date.
- Didn't wanna make this one.
(Leonard:)Look on the bright side, she might
turn out to be a nice, beautiful girl.
Great, we get married,
I won't be able to talk to her...
(Raj:)...and we'll spend the rest of our lives
in total silence.
It worked for my parents.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
- Hi, guys.
- Oh, hey.
I need guinea pigs.
(Sheldon:)Okay, there's a lab animal supply
company in Reseda you could try.
(Sheldon:)But if your research is going to have
human applications, I suggest white mice.
(Sheldon:)Their brain chemistry
is far closer to ours.
(Penny:)I swear to God, Sheldon, one day,
I'm gonna get the hang of talking to you.
(Leonard:)His mom's been saying that for years.
(Leonard:)- What's up?
- Well, I convinced the restaurant...
...to give me a bartending shift
so I need to practice mixing drinks.
Oh, well, great. The key to acquiring
proficiency in any task is repetition.
(Sheldon:)With certain obvious exceptions.
(Sheldon:)Suicide, for example.